A Guide to the Papers of J. Calvitt Clarke, 1918-1970
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: Literary Manuscripts
  - Subseries B: Manuscripts of Jeanne Clarke Wood
    - A Study of the Tragedy of King Richard the Third by Jeanne Clarke Wood, n. d., 1 item. (Box-folder 11:6)
    - Three Blind Wives by Jeanne Clarke Wood, n. d., 1 item. (Box-folder 11:7)
    - The Ugly American by Jeanne Clarke Wood. Book review, 1960, 1 item. (Box-folder 11:8)
    - Untitled by Jeanne Clarke Wood, n. d., 2 items. (Box-folder 11:9)
      Included is correspondence on the elements of writing.
    - Untitled [Beginnings of novels: Drina] by Jeanne Clarke Wood, n. d., 1 item. (Box-folder 11:10)
    - Untitled [Beginnings of novels: Kate, Mystery] by Jeanne Clarke Wood, n. d., 1 item. (Box-folder 11:11)
    - Untitled by Jeanne Clarke Wood, n. d., 1 item. (Box-folder 11:12)
    - Untitled by Jeanne Clarke Wood Chapters 1-13, n. d., 1 item. (Box-folder 11:13)
    - Untitled by Jeanne Clarke Wood Chapter 14-22, n. d., 1 item. (Box-folder 11:14)
    - Untitled by Jeanne Clarke Wood, 1949, 4 items. (Box-folder 11:15)
    - Vacation for Two by Jeanne Clarke Wood, n. d., 3 items. (Box-folder 11:16)
      Included is correspondence with Elmer and Caroline about editorial advice.
    - The World We Live In by Jeanne Clarke Wood, 1960, 1 item. 7 pp. (Box-folder 12:1)
    - Miscellaneous. Black Boy by Richard Wright; Dust Jacket and excerpt, n. d., 1 item. (Box-folder 12:2)
    - Publishing Correspondence Jeanne Clarke Wood, 1938-1950, 26 items. (Box-folder 12:3)
    - Publishing Edison Tesla Marshall, 1949-1960, 38 items. (Box-folder 12:4)
    - Herman E. "Jack" Wood's Medical School Slides, n. d., 81 items. (Box-folder 13:1)
    - Herman E. "Jack" Wood's Medical School Slides, n. d., 81 items. (Box-folder 13:2)
    - Herman E. "Jack" Wood Medical School Slides, n. d., 61 items. (Box-folder 13:3)